Tim Phillips, Designer

About

I'm a designer with an intrinsic passion for creating intuitive digital platforms and the systems that enable them.

I believe any problem can be solved when focusing on the users within the given problem space.

Throughout my process, I work horizontally across research, design, engineering and business, allowing me to constantly adapt and iterate to ensure the final outcome is aligned, tested and proven.

Contact

Email <u>timphillips1991@gmail.com</u>
Web <u>timphillipsdesign.com.au</u>
Phone +61 409 888 443

Education

Bachelor of Design (2012)
Communication Design
Swinburne University of Technology

Diploma of Graphic Design (2010 - 2011) Swinburne University of Technology

Resumé

Experience

<u>Carsales</u> (2021 - present)

I'm currently working as the product designer in the carsales SELECT team, designing their consumer facing product across web and native platforms. The SELECT project aims to enable consumers to complete more parts of the car buying journey online.

<u>Assembler</u> (2020 - 2021)

I worked as the Lead Product Designer for Assembler. Leading the design across their range of platforms, as well as creating their design system. I also supported the engineering team with front-end web development.

PwC Australia (2018 - 2020)

Working within PwC Australia's New Ventures unit, I led the design and front-end web development within the Automation Engine team.

We worked on a platform used by internal teams, that enabled them to build and manage web applications.

The Just Group (2017 - 2018)

Predominantly worked on the Smiggle brand, designing web and email content for their global market base (AU, UK, IRE and Asia at the time). Also working across the Just Group's other core brands in varying capacities.

View prior experience